

JESSICA NATIONS

WEB DEVELOPER | ST. LOUIS, MO

OBJECTIVE

Versatile Web Designer and Developer who consistently demonstrates a high attention to detail combined with a knowledge of Python, HTML, CSS, SQL, C#/ASP.Net, and an extensive customer service background seeks a position where experience, motivation, and commitment to excellence will be utilized.

SKILLS

programming languages:

- Python
- C#/ASP.Net

tools and technologies:

- GitHub
- MAMP
- Moqups
- Trello

IDE:

- Visual Studio
 database administration:
 - SQL

PROJECTS

Z00 WEBSITE • LAUNCHCODE • 6/2018 - 9/2018

I rebuilt an outdated, text-based website and gave it user-focused features with room to grow. It now looks more professional and could help drive traffic and improve business.

https://github.com/JessicaNations/BigJoelSafari

EXPERIENCE

WAREHOUSE CLERK • CBRE • 10/2017 - PRESENT

I compiled and helped write the mailroom policy and procedure that is used nationwide. I researched and helped order new mail carts. I created the training materials for X-Ray operation training.

CIRCULATION ASSISTANT AND LIBRARY CLERK • ST. LOUIS COUNTY LIBRARY • 06/2014 - 10/2017

I was one on a team of 3-5 librarians that did everything from creating library cards, providing customer assistance, shelving the materials, helping with library programs, and maintaining the sale shelf.

EDUCATION

LAUNCHCODE 101 • 06/2018 • LAUNCHCODE HEADQUARTERS

BACHELORS OF FINE ARTS DEGREE IN MUSIC HISTORY AND LITERATURE • 12/2011 • SIUE

MASTERS OF LIBRARY AND INFORMATION SCIENCE • 05/2013 • UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS URBANA-CHAMPAIGN







